Okay, okay, let's take a picture.
よ いしょ、よいしょ、撮っちゃうね、
this.
これ
tits.
おっぱい
I wanted to get a room early.
早くお部屋取りたかった
I'd like you to deliver.
出前して欲しいな
Wait a minute.
ちょっと待ってね
What can I do?
何していいですか?
何していい?
No more teasing.
もうじらしなし
I am often told that my pussy is beautiful.
マンコ綺麗ってよく言われます
thank you.
ありがとう
Because everyone uses it beautifully.
みんなが綺麗に使ってくれるからだよ
It feels so good.
めちゃめちゃ気持ちいい
It's not like her pussy is loose.
マンコガバガバじゃないもん
Feels good.
気持ちいい
You can put it in until now.
今まで入れていいよ
It's okay to jerk off.
シコシコしていいよ
I've been waiting so let's hurry.
待たしちゃったから早くしよう
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Oh no, it might come out today.
やばい、今日すぐ出ちゃうかもしれない
Let me pay for Minami's pussy.
南のマンコ払わせて
After I got some power from rapping.
ラップでパワー入った後ね
What can I do?
何していいよ
Oh no, let's make it stronger.
やばい、強くしちゃおう
I think I'll go right away today.
今日マジですぐ行っちゃうと思う
Wait a minute.
ちょっと待ってね
terrible.
やばい
I went there a lot, all of a sudden.
いっぱい行っちゃったよ、いきなり
Do you want to see fours?
四つん台見たいの?
Wait a minute.
ちょっと待ってね
I think I'll go on all fours.
四つん台しようかな
For now, the pussy.
とりあえずマンコが
appear?
見える?
It's soaking wet though.
びしょびしょなんだけど
Look.
ほら
terrible
やばい
Yo, already.
よ、 もう
I wiped it all down.
めっちゃ拭いちゃった
Minami is a good girl, really.
南いい子だよね、本当にね
I think I'll do it on all fours.
四つん台でしようかな
I want to wait already.
もう待ちたい
I'm full.
お腹いっぱい
Throat You can't see my dick.
喉 チンコなんか見えないでしょ
Do you want to put dick in it?
チンチン入れたい?
You can put the safe in your mouth.
口にセーフ出していいよ
Shall we have a quick chat?
つぼつぼしようか
Do you want to see a close-up of your pussy?
おマンコアップ見たいの?
When your pussy is up, When your pussy is up,
おマンコアップしたら、 おマンコアップしたら、
You know, there's some kind of hair on it.
あれね、なんか髪の毛ついてる
When I close up my pussy, it's jibobobo.
おマンコアップしたら、じぼぼぼね
Shall we jibobobo?
じぼぼぼしようか
Wait a moment, I'll make a par.
パーするからちょっと待って
That's right, I added too much.
それな、量つけすぎたよね
Are you still holding back, Minami?
まだ我慢してんの、南が
That Minami is holding back Chin Chin,
あの南がチンチンを我慢しているのよ、
still.
まだ
It became slimy.
ぬるぬるになっちゃった
Yes, it's par.
はい、パーです
It's bubbly.
つぼぼぼするね
I want to salt it once.
一回塩ふきたい
Can I salt it?
塩ふいていい?
It came out a lot again.
まためっちゃ出ちゃった
Isn't it dangerous?
やばくね?
What do you think, like now?
どうだ、今みたいな
Shadesha.
でしゃでしゃ
This is terrible.
やばいよ
This is something like this.
これは、なんかこの、これ
After all, this is something that's not very fun.
これだって、これがなんかあんまふけないやつなんでね、
I forgot the skin-colored one I always use and brought it with me.
いつも使ってる肌色のやつを忘れちゃって持ってくるの
That's better though.
あれのほうがいいんだけどさ
Hi, I'm glad.
ひ じょういするね
fire
ひ
I'll give it a try.
じ ょういするね
I don't really feel like it and it hurts, but this...
なんかあんま気持ちがないし、痛いんだけどこれ
The usual one is good.
いつものやつがいい
I can't do this.
これできない
Chin Chin is too hard and I can't do it.
チンチンが固すぎてできなくなる
I can't do this unless it's on camera, so can I stop doing this?
カメラ上じゃないといけばこれ無理だからやめていいですか?
I don't feel like it at all.
全然気持ちくない
It's called half cut.
半切れっていうね
I really don't like it that much.
ひじょういそんな好きじゃないっすな
I prefer to do it normally with chin chin.
普通にチンチンでやるほうが好きだわ
Is it okay if I wait in front?
前待ちでいい?
This rail video is no good.
このレール動画ダメだもん
I hate this person.
この人嫌い
It hurts when I hit it.
叩くて痛い
Someone please mess with me.
しっくり誰かいじってよ
It's only just begun.
まだ始まったばっかだよね
I've been doing it for an hour.
1時間やってるよ
I think it will take about another hour.
あと1時間くらいやると思う
perhaps.
たぶん
I still peed, so please wait a moment.
まだ おしっこしたからちょっと待ってて
Are you the type of person who can feel good with a dick?
チクビで気持ちよくなれるタイプの人ですか?
Chikubi prefers being touched by someone.
チクビは誰かに触ってもらうほうが好き
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
Wait till you go.
行くまで待って
It came out soon.
もうすぐ出た
It's a bit serious.
ちょっとマジでやばい
It looks like a puddle.
水たまりみたいになってる
I'm home.
ただいま
I'm not going out anymore.
もう出ない
I'll go out after drinking tea.
お茶飲んだら出るよ